Finally, the movement of brain development will truly
最终，大脑发育的运动将会给我们
give meaning, I could say, to cranial osteopathy.
真正赋予颅骨整骨疗法以意义，我可以说。
I can put it that way.
我可以这样说。
That the body, it has done well, it knows well, and therefore we will simply, it is it that will instruct you
身体，它做得很好，它很了解，所以我们只需，它会指导你们
in the pathways.
沿着这些路径。
It is not you who will re-instruct the brain; it knows the way.
不是你们去重新指导大脑，它知道路径。
But somewhere, it has within itself this kind of pathway.
但在某种程度上，它内在拥有这种路径。
And so we will learn to...
所以我们将学习如何...
to perform the brain's tai chi; we will see that the cranial base is dependent
进行大脑的太极，我们将看到颅底依赖于
on the brain,
大脑，
we will see that the entire system of establishment, the ventricular system,
我们将看到整个建立系统，脑室系统，
the deep fluidic system of the brain, is dependent on the dynamic movement of the
大脑深层的液体系统，依赖于大脑的动态运动，
brain,
大脑，
and we will see that the entire membranous system, thus all the tension membranes,
我们还将看到整个膜系统，也就是所有张力膜，
falx cerebri, tentorium cerebelli, falx cerebelli,
大脑镰，小脑幕，小脑镰，
the dural membranes, parietal, visceral.
硬脑膜、顶骨膜、脏层膜。
All of this, all this compartmentalization of the brain, we could say,
所有这些，大脑的这种分区化，可以说，
will again be dependent on the dynamics of this brain.
将再次依赖于这个大脑的动态。
From, we could say, the dense structure located at the level of the cranial base
从，可以说，位于颅底平面上的密集结构
of the skull,
颅骨，
up to the vault; next time, we will review, meaning we will essentially study
直到颅顶，下次我们将回顾，也就是说我们将主要研究
the visceral system.
内脏。
We see that the transverse septum would integrate
我们看到横膈将整合
the tissue, thus the heart, the diaphragm, and it continued with the
组织，也就是心脏、膈肌，并与
falciform ligament.
镰状韧带相连。
So we already have an integration between the heart and the liver in their function.
所以我们已经有了心脏和肝脏在功能上的整合。
Furthermore, it continued further posteriorly via the hiatus of Winslow and the entire
此外，它还通过网膜孔向后延伸，以及整个
great movement to form the greater omentum.
大运动以形成大网膜。
This means we have a relationship between the heart, the diaphragm, the brain, and the immune system
这意味着心脏、膈肌、大脑和免疫系统之间存在关系
peritoneal.
腹膜的。
This means that the core or the cranial base can destabilize an immune system.
这意味着颅底或其核心区域可能导致免疫系统不稳定。
Furthermore, the highest immune system is the tonsillar system, with Waldeyer's ring,
此外，上部免疫系统，即扁桃体系统，与韦氏环相关联，
which is situated superiorly.
它位于上方。
This means that if you have a dysfunction located here, you will even observe that on a level,
这意味着如果此处出现功能障碍，你甚至会发现在某个层面上，
depending on the frequency you attune to, if you consider it on a molecular level, you will see...
这取决于你所关注的频率，如果你从分子层面来看，你会发现...
many children with ENT issues,
许多有耳鼻喉科问题的儿童，
ultimately, you will find
最终你会发现
on a molecular level, the same immunoglobulin,
在分子层面上存在相同的免疫球蛋白，
namely, immunoglobulin
即免疫球蛋白
of type 1, I believe,
我认为是1型，
which will be found at the cecal level.
它会出现在盲肠层面上。
That is to say, a destabilization of the
也就是说，
peritoneum can
腹膜的不稳定可能
in fact, destabilize the entire
实际上导致整个
ENT sphere. In other words, this means
耳鼻喉区域不稳定。换句话说，这意味着
that from a practical standpoint,
在实践层面上，
to rebalance an
为了重新平衡
ENT sphere, one must rebalance the peritoneum,
耳鼻喉区域，需要重新平衡腹膜，
and more specifically, the cecal level,
更具体地说，是盲肠层面。
which contains, on the appendicular level, lymphatic tissues
它在阑尾层面上包含
that are exactly the same.
完全相同的淋巴组织。
Furthermore, at one time, tonsils were removed, and appendectomies were performed.
此外，在当时有一段时间，人们会切除扁桃体和阑尾。
And this occurs in synchronous, synchronous movements, you see, which will
你看，这发生在同步的、
develop.
会发展的同步运动中。
Furthermore, you now have everything concerning the esophageal relationship.
此外，现在还有食管方面的所有关联。
So we see that this esophageal mesenchyme, this is what we covered yesterday.
因此我们看到，这种食管间充质，也就是我们昨天所做的，
disrupt the function of the diaphragm.
会扰乱膈肌的功能。
So this means that the stomach,
这意味着胃，
the esophagus, suspended up to the cranial base,
食管，悬挂至颅底，
via what are called the carotid influences,
通过我们所说的颈动脉相关作用力，
the pterygoid plexuses,
翼状神经丛，
and even up to the level of the pterygoids superiorly,
甚至到上方的翼骨，
is suspended.
是悬挂的。
Therefore, any destabilization of your cranial base
因此，你颅底的任何不稳定
can disrupt cardiotuberositary function.
都可能扰乱心肺功能。
And thus disrupt diaphragmatic movement,
从而扰乱膈肌运动，
which is a very important movement.
这是一种非常重要的运动。
You also have another important aspect, which is what we call the mesoblastic wall,
你还有另一个同样重要的事情，那就是我们所说的中胚层壁，
the lateral wall.
侧壁。
This means that the entire costal cage is completely dependent on the
这意味着整个肋骨架完全依赖于
proper functioning of your diaphragm.
你膈肌的良好功能。
Therefore, this means that the entire dorsal region, in fact, will be dependent on this.
因此，这意味着整个背部区域实际上都将依赖于此。
Furthermore, in this regard, we observed a junction with the kidney, with
此外，与此相关，我们看到与肾脏有一个连接，
respect to the psoas, and thus with respect to the kidney.
与腰大肌相关，因此与肾脏相关。
and therefore with respect to your duodenum.
从而与你的十二指肠相关。
This therefore demonstrates a global integrity.
这表明它是一个整体的完整性。
What we must remember is that we must learn to work with this diaphragm
我们应该记住的是，我们必须学会锻炼这个膈肌
more than we believe, with greater subtlety, remotely or not,
比我们想象的更精细，无论是在远处还是近处，
and that if we manage to expand this diaphragm, you improve the quality of life.
如果我们能够扩张这个膈肌，你就能改善生活质量。
However, I felt comfortable with the notochord reference
尽管如此，我对脊索的参考感觉很好
for the first exercise, as it creates,
对于第一个练习，因为它创造了，
where you had explained the open door after the point.
你曾向我们解释了点之后的开门。
mobile after point 0
0点后的移动
which forms 1, whereas there, in the diaphragm,
形成1，同样地，在膈肌中，
I did not feel a reference
我没有感觉到任何参考
on which to base myself, apart from
可以依靠的，除了
the notochord, ultimately, to rediscover
脊索，最终，为了找回
this unity in my
我体内的这种统一性在我的
center, I have the work.
中心，我有了工作。
I think the first point of reference
我认为第一个参考点
that you must have, is to try
你必须做的，就是尝试
to find the fulcrum of the diaphragm.
找到膈肌的支点。
I tried to show you
我试图向你们展示
that we could suspend this fulcrum
我们可以将这个支点悬浮
to the dynamic stillness
在动态的静止中
of space. It's like a door
空间。这就像一扇门
that opens and closes. And so, if it's a door that opens, it means there's a
打开又关闭。所以，如果这是一扇打开的门，那就意味着有一个
hinge. If there's a hinge, it means there's a 'hitch point',
铰链。如果有一个铰链，那就意味着有一个“连接点”，
a fulcrum.
一个支点。
A fulcrum, initially, which is a bit mobile, but if you go further and further,
一个支点，最初有点活动，但如果你走得越来越远，
it becomes a fixed point. Well, that's it, that's your reference point. But,
它就变成了一个固定点。嗯，就是这样，这是你的参考点。但是，
that you must suspend to the dynamic stillness of the system.
你必须将其悬浮在系统的动态静止中。
As if there's a question, is it in the mesentery,
好像有一个问题，在肠系膜中，
including the vena cava or not?
是否包括腔静脉？
No, it's very close. The heart, it's quite...
不，它非常近。心脏，它相当...
You see, you even have an axis, you almost have an axis, you see?
你看，你甚至有一个轴，你几乎有一个轴，你明白吗？
An axis of the vena cava, you look at a heart, you see?
腔静脉的轴，你看着心脏，明白吗？
So it's very close in relation to the liver level.
所以它与肝脏的水平非常接近。
There's a small distance, in fact, between the vena cava and the...
事实上，腔静脉和...之间有一小段距离。
He described to us the first great movement of an autocorn and this second movement
他向我们描述了自发角（autocorne）的第一个大运动，以及这第二个运动
that we saw yesterday in my little mushroom film, of the
我们昨天在我的小蘑菇电影中看到的，关于
amniotic cavity that will go around.
羊膜腔将进行环绕。
So a second movement, it goes in both directions. We could say that the center of this movement
所以第二个运动，它向两个方向发展。我们可以说这个运动的中心
at the visceral level, is it at the level of the...
在内脏层面，它是在...的层面吗？
It's the heart.
是心脏。
It's the heart and the peritoneum.
是心脏和腹膜。
so the image is that you wrap yourself
所以这个意象就是你缠绕着
around your cardio-pleuro-peritoneal system
围绕着你的心胸腹膜系统
you really have to see that as a joint
你真的需要把它看作一个关节
it is an articulation
这是一个关节
simultaneously, your intrinsic core
同时你的自身核心
simultaneously, your neural tube develops very robustly anteriorly
同时你的神经管非常非常强烈地向前发展
it is this development that brings
是它带来了
the heart, as you see here
心脏，你在这里看到
but posteriorly, your neural tube also grows
但你的神经管后方也在生长
it is this growth that brings the allantois
是它带来了尿囊
through a field of restriction
通过一个限制场
on the anterior plane
在前方平面上
thus, you come towards
所以你走向
you come to fold back upon yourself
你再次汇合
closed as if by your embryonic pedicle; you have achieved this, thus you bring back
被你的胚胎蒂所封闭，你做到了，所以你带回
all of this is truly this
所有这一切，这确实是这个
image, we truly see it here, and that is where we integrate its allantois at the same time as we will
图像，我们在这里确实看到，正是在这里我们将尿囊整合进来，同时我们也将
integrate the heart; it becomes a fulcrum, but at that moment, you
心脏整合进来，这成为一个支点，但此时你
will have two important phenomena
将会有两件重要的事情
namely, you will have not only the heart pushing on
那就是你不仅会有心脏来推动
the superior part
上部
of the vitelline vesicle; you see, it originates here, it pushes, by
卵黄囊的上部，你看，它从这里开始，它推动，在
pushing this, it orientates the tissue located posteriorly,
推动它的过程中，这会引导后面的组织，
which is called the septum transversum, whose origin was already present; if you will, the cells were already there,
它被称为横膈膜，它的起源已经存在，如果你愿意，细胞已经存在，
but it will orient and organize it; thus, it is the encounter of the brain with the heart,
但这会引导和组织它，所以这是大脑与心脏的相遇，
and of the heart with the superior part of the vitelline vesicle, which will provide the impulse,
以及心脏与卵黄囊上部的相遇，这将提供冲动，
for the tissue that forms your septum transversum.
用于形成你的横膈膜的组织。
This signifies that the heart is an articulation between the brain and the diaphragm.
这意味着心脏是大脑和膈肌之间的关节。